http://www.christikon.org/toc-privacy/#privacy

Skip to content
T&C / PrivacyDavid2018-10-29T21:28:24-06:00Terms and Conditions of UseYour usage of contents of this web site is conditional on your acceptance of the following terms. If you do not accept the terms, refrain from using any of the contents, documents and/or information.All of the information, documents, graphics, brochures, web pages, press releases, forms, etc. (collectively referred to as “documents”) located on this web site in any form are ©copyrighted with all rights reserved.Documents are intellectual property of their creators and all of the rights are reserved by the appropriate companies unless noted otherwise. You are permitted to view the documents for conducting your normal course of business however all copyright notices shall remain intact.You may not re-distribute the documents in anyway that would conflict with the copyright notices. You may not use the documents in competition with or to reverse engineer the products or services of Lutheran Bible Camp, Inc. doing business as Christikon.The documents are provided “as is”. Documents could contain errors or omissions and Lutheran Bible Camp, nor any of their employees or associates, or other companies creating the documents, make any warranty, express or implied, or assume any legal liability or responsibility for but not limited to the correctness, accuracy, completeness, or usefulness for your usage of the documents or any information that they contain.Lutheran Bible Camp, Inc. reserves the rights to change the specifications in their respective documents or their contents from time to time without any notices.Privacy StatementLutheran Bible Camp, Inc. operates the christikon.org and growchristikon.org websites, which provide the SERVICE.This page is used to inform website visitors regarding our policies with the collection, use, and disclosure of Personal Information if anyone decided to use our Service.If you choose to use our Service, then you agree to the collection and use of information in relation with this policy. The Personal Information that we collect are used for providing and improving the Service. We will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.The terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, which is accessible at our websites, unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy.Information Collection and UseFor a better experience while using our Service, we may require you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information, including but not limited to your name, phone number, and postal address. The information that we collect will be used to contact or identify you.Log DataWe want to inform you that whenever you visit our Service, we collect information that your browser sends to us that is called Log Data. This Log Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser version, pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages, and other statistics.CookiesCookies are files with small amount of data that is commonly used an anonymous unique identifier. These are sent to your browser from the website that you visit and are stored on your computer’s hard drive.Our website uses these “cookies” to collection information and to improve our Service. You have the option to either accept or refuse these cookies, and know when a cookie is being sent to your computer. If you choose to refuse our cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Service.Service ProvidersWe may employ third-party companies and individuals due to the following reasons:To facilitate our ServiceTo provide the Service on our behalfTo perform Service-related servicesTo assist us in analyzing how our Service is usedWe want to inform our Service users that these third parties have access to your Personal Information. The reason is to perform the tasks assigned to them on our behalf. However, they are obligated not to disclose or use the information for any other purpose.SecurityWe value your trust in providing us your Personal Information, thus we are striving to use commercially acceptable means of protecting it. But remember that no method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure and reliable, and we cannot guarantee its absolute security.Links to Other SitesOur Service may contain links to other sites. If you click on a third-party link, you will be directed to that site. Note that these external sites are not operated by us. Therefore, we strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of these websites. We have no control over, and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third-party sites or services.Children’s PrivacyOur Services do not address anyone under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect personal identifiable information from children under 13. In the case we discover that a child under 13 has provided us with personal information, we immediately delete this from our servers. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your child has provided us with personal information, please contact us so that we will be able to do necessary actions.Changes to This Privacy PolicyWe may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. Thus, we advise you to review this page periodically for any changes. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page. These changes are effective immediately, after they are posted on this page.Contact UsIf you have any questions or suggestions about our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact us.
Join the Paper Mailing ListUse this form to be added to our mailing list for receiving news and information about Christikon in printed form via US Mail Service. This form is for mailing list ONLY.Name*
First
Last
New / Update*Is this new information or updating an existing contact info?NewUpdateAddress*
Street Address
Address Line 2
City
AlabamaAlaskaArizonaArkansasCaliforniaColoradoConnecticutDelawareDistrict of ColumbiaFloridaGeorgiaHawaiiIdahoIllinoisIndianaIowaKansasKentuckyLouisianaMaineMarylandMassachusettsMichiganMinnesotaMississippiMissouriMontanaNebraskaNevadaNew HampshireNew JerseyNew MexicoNew YorkNorth CarolinaNorth DakotaOhioOklahomaOregonPennsylvaniaRhode IslandSouth CarolinaSouth DakotaTennesseeTexasUtahVermontVirginiaWashingtonWest VirginiaWisconsinWyomingArmed Forces AmericasArmed Forces EuropeArmed Forces Pacific
State
ZIP Code
PhoneEmail
Go to Top
